So now I'm going to paint the other eye, start off, oil in, okay, so I'm just going to put the
purple ring shape in, just going to take the white of the eye, a bit higher, purple,
too light, come back down, save it some red, burnt umber, and decide the lid, okay,
decide edge, it's a bit higher, okay, decided the eye lid, it's a bit darker,
towards the edge, that's a light in there, okay, and looking around these shapes,
the separation between the brown and the lid, and this side of the lid tone,
a bit too far, let's push that down a bit, okay, and the crease and the lid, slightly lighter around here,
you can see that lid, it's almost like halfway between the inner and purple, and I'm just
going to indicate that bit of that crease shape, goes into the brow, okay, put that accent in,
some alizarin, touch of green, put that down, make this eye a bit darker, get this into the corner,
lid sorry, pick out the highlight, okay, bottom lid, so the top lid, a bit more on the alizarin side,
purple in there, in just a bit lighter, a bit warmer, around the lid, and the side of the lid,
some green in there, get a slightly lighter, you decide the lid there, you've got the luscious,
kind of quite warm, and you've got the luscious top lid, you've got violet,
some orange in there, violet, purple, and green somber, got the, so iris, blue, orange,
and bad day, purple, that white of the eye, okay, highlights, a bit darker, so that's the eye.